如行尸走肉般被人遗忘
He's sleepwalking into oblivion
非法移民和通膨失控
Uncontrolled migration, hyper-inflation
罪犯猖獗
rampant crime
文化马克斯主义渗透我们
rampant crime, cultural Marxists..
五点钟 该上场了
Here we go. The 5.00pm.
没问题吧  -没问题 格雷格
All good?   -yeah, I'm good, Greg
这是洛根死后 我第一次竞选
considering it's my first post-Logan election
希德到处荼毒抹黑我
and I have Cyd running around town
活像条拿着智能手机的眼镜蛇
spitting poison like a fucking king cobra with an i Phone.
我左有PGN右有FVA
I have PGN to the left of me, and I have FVA to the right
我得交出史上最漂亮的选票数字
I gotta deliver the best election numbers ever
因为 我老板想挖出我的心 祭旗
cause my bosses wanna rip my heart out as a peace offering to all comers
所以 格雷格 你知道吗 我现在有点紧绷
so, no, Greg, you know, I'm a little bit tense.
有一丝 一丁点紧绷
Just a little bit. A little bit tense.
我觉得很不错
Well, yeah, I'm feel in 'pretty good
继   承   之   战
第 4 季  第 8 集
我11点到投票所
I got to the polling location at 11.00am.
觉得很奇怪 因为人太少了
I thought it was very odd that the line was so short
嘿 汤姆  -嘿 肯
Hey, Tom.   -Hey, Ken.
你还好吗 感觉不错吧
You good? You feeling good?
晚上要全力出击 知道吗
Needs to be gangbusters tonight, man, yeah?
是的 没问题 没问题
Yeah. You got it, you got it.
我需要那些数字 阿汤
All right. Need those numbers, T.
我真的想看到那些数学 汤姆
Really wanna see those numbers, Tom.
好吗 市场正在关注  -好的
Okay? Market's watching.   -Okay
看这第一次 超级杯我们少了国王 还能不能发挥战力
First Super Bowl, how we gonna cope without the king, right?
知道了 肯 没问题 没问题
Okay, got it, Ken. All good, all good
嘿 阿潘 情况如何
Hey, Pam. How's it looking?
有点杂音
A bit of crackle.
我们有辆转播车 在俄勒冈碰到一点问题
We have a news van in a bit of trouble in Oregon
密尔瓦基情况有点火爆
Things looking fight y in Milwaukee.
你有没有看到那段暴红视频 有个女人
Did you see the viral thing about the woman
冒用亡母的名字 投了四十次票 给希门尼斯
who voted, like, 40 times for Jimenez under her dead mom's name?
我们找到她了 消息不是很可靠
We tracked her down. Not super reliable
她的身体并不好  -她…
She's not a well person.   -She's..
阿潘 你又不是医生
Well, you're not a doctor, Pam.
考到执照前 不如请她受访
Until you qualify, why don't you get her on the air?
穿着皮鞋度过漫漫长夜吗
Long night in dress shoes?
希德以前都是穿厚袜子和懒人鞋
Cyd used to go for these sort of slip-ons with a padded sock
那可能是因为 她那双蹄子
Yeah, probably 'cause she couldn't get her cloven hooves
穿不了正常的鞋子
into her regular shoes.
阿潘 我这样很舒服
I'm perfectly comfortable, Pam
我的足弓很好
I've got good arches.
被人称赞过
They've been remarked upon.
五点钟出口民调 快点五点了
5.00pm exit polls. Come on, 5.00pm
嘿 达温...你...没事的
Hey, Darwin, you don't... Oh, they're cool
你今晚不会做什么特别的准备吧
You don't... You don't do anything special tonight, do you?
因为 刚刚有人提到 成人纸尿裤
It's just somebody was talking about adult diapers?
不用 我觉得 一定能找到时间上洗手间的
Oh, no, I think there's always time for the bathroom
好 谢了
Fine. Okay. Thanks.
不好意思 借过 借过 借过
Okay, excuse me. Coming through. Coming through here, coming-through
嘿 各位 我要讲一下条款与规定
Hey, everybody. So, terms and conditions.
已经知道的人 请忍耐一下
Forgive me, those of you who already know this.
你有休息吧
Did you get... get some rest, though?
没有 夫妻吵架
No. No, marital strife
听懂的人请说一声
Can I hear a "got it "?
懂了
Got it.
谢谢 另外...
Thank you. Also.
你晚上过得如何
How was your night?
跟马特森吗 很可怕
With Matsson? Pretty monstrous
他的那帮人 知道一些不入流的地方
His crew knows some unseemly venues
我跟一个老头子跳了舞
I danced with an old man.
什么
What?
对 他不想跳
Yeah, he didn't wanna dance
但他们逼着我们跳了
but they made us dance
他很困惑
He was so confused.
我喝了一些…
I drank... things that.
平常不是用来喝的东西
aren't normally drinks
我觉得...
And I... I got the impression...
你知不知道 马特森和小西之间...
Do you know about Matsson with Shiv and their sort of
他们的商业结盟协议
like, their... their business alliance agreement?
我不知道你在说什么
Well, I'm sure I don't know what you're talking about.
我也觉得你不知道
Okay, I didn't think so.
要不要讨论一下对策
You wanna strategize?
狠狠的整她一下
You wanna fry her ass up?
格雷格 情报…
Information, Greg
像一瓶好酒
It's like a bottle of fine wine.
存着积着 等到特别场合再拿出来
You store it, you hoard it, you save it for a special occasion.
用它打烂某人的脸
And then you smash someone's fuckin'face in with it.
漂亮
Nice.
我们听说的是...
So, what we're hearing is..
记得 这不是确切结果
and remember, this is not decisive
门肯在天治亚
what we're seeing is Mencken
和亚利葵那的表现 可能好得超乎预期
may be over performing in Georgia and Arizona.
所以 早期预测是 结果可能比之前想的更接近
So, our early read would be closer than polls have suggested
很接近 但希门尼斯很可能会略胜一筹
Close, but Jimenez likely edging on what we've seen.
听着 这是机密资讯
Listen, this is privileged information.
走漏消息影响选情
Leaks that suppress or encourage turn out
可能会让我们 被国家选举报道团除名
could result in our ejection from the National Election Pool
好吗  -好
Okay?   -Yeah.
你们都听到了 要守口如瓶
Yeah, you heard the man. Zip it.
很好
That's great.
好的 汤姆说 依照出口民调结果 胜选的应该是希门尼斯
Okay, Tom says exit polls say looks like Jimenez.
别走漏消息  -太好了
No leaks.   -That's great.
吉尔传了四个笑脸符号给我 他们觉得赢定了
I mean, I got four smileys from Gil. They think they've got it
门肯传了两根茄子和一面旗子给我
Well, I have got eggplant, eggplant, flag from Mencken.
两根茄子比不上四个笑脸 这很明显
Well, two eggplants is not as much as four smileys, obviously
四个笑脸表示了
Four smileys is symptomatic
他与现实脱节的竞选团队的自满
of the complacency at the heart of his out-of-touch campaign.
两根茄子和一面旗子显示了 他们仇视女性的虚张声势
Eggplant, eggplant, flag reeks of the misogynistic bravado
中间选民十分厌恶这点
that has so repelled the median voter
天啊 我不舒服
Jesus. Ah, I feel sick
为什么 很好玩啊
Oh, why? It's fun.
我的队伍在跟你的队伍对战
My team's playing your team.
刺激之处就在于 我的队伍获胜时
It's only spicy 'cause if my team wins
会枪杀你的队伍
they're gonna shoot your team.
但你听到什么风声
Okay, but what are you hearing, seriously?
这些是 你方的 纳粹车子吗
Are these your vans, the Nazi vans?
车? 你是说快乐专车吗
The van? Oh, the... the fun vans?
快乐巴士 对
The... The fun buses? Yeah
对 在佛罗里达 那些车子去接人
Yeah, in Florida they picked people up
说要带他们去投票
telling them they were taking them to vote
结果 有个小孩在高速公路上被赶下去了
and then a kid got left by the highway
罗曼 这他妈是绑架
It's fucking kidnapping, Rome
现在变成他妈绑架了?
It's fucking kidnapping now?
是栽脏 你想得美
False flag. Nice try
绑架 居然说是绑架
Kidnapping. It's kidnapping
嘿  -卢卡斯 嘿
-Hey.   -Lukas, hey
看样子 希门尼斯会赢
So, it's looking like Jimenez
这对民主是好事 对我们更好
which is good for democracy and great for us
不管怎样 我们该考虑...
So, either way, I think that we consider releasing your..
明天公布你的假数据
you know, your funky numbers may be tomorrow
或是后天
Day after tomorrow.
先发制人
Just get ahead of the numbers
我可以想想要怎么说
and, you know, I can come up with some language
昨天晚上...
Yeah, I was... I was talking..
我跟奥斯卡和格雷格瑞·佩格瑞讲到这件事
I ast night to Oskar and Gregory Peggory about that
抱歉 你跟格雷格谈这件事?
I'm sorry, you spoke to Greg about this?
他是以正常派的身份参与对话
Yeah, well, he was part of a conversation just as a normal ist
是的 然后我就在想 或许
And... yeah, then I was wondering, you know, maybe we.
不要把我见不得人的秘密公诸于世 比较好
maybe we keep my... my terrible secret a secret, you know?
好吧…
Okay...
这样吧 让我想一下
Yeah, look, let me have a think about that
我得接个电话 待会儿再打给你
I gotta... I gotta take this. I'll... I'll call you back
纳特 丹佛任务控制中心的情况如何
Nate. How's things in Mission Control Denver?
小西 你在泛美网科吗
Are you in at ATN, Shiv?
在楼上
Upstairs.
放手让他们去做 这是爸的规矩
Leave it to them. Dad's rules
他们必须报道恐吓事件
Well, they need to be covering the intimidation s
小西 这真是暗黑到一个地步
It's pretty dark, Shiv.
谁监视警卫 我啊
Who watches the watchmen? I fucking do
数据漂亮吗
Are you getting good numbers?
很好 我在看气象
Good. Just watching the weather.
乌云在内华达州集结
Storm clouds in Nevada
我们控制住了
We got people in line
威斯康辛也有动荡 但是
A disturbance in Wisconsin, but.
对 很害怕 但情况很好
Yeah, scared but good.
地区数据是…
Precinct data's..
宾夕法尼亚 和亚利桑那 可能是硬仗
Pennsylvania, Arizona could be tough
我们保持联络
Let's keep this channel open.
讨论马特森 我 还有改革泛美网科的事
On all things Matsson and me and the new ATN, yeah?
讨论所有的好事
All things good
好 希门尼斯胜选
All right, so Jimenez wins
手一挥 通过交易
and he just waves the fuckin' deal through
那我们怎么办
and then we're what?
做困兽之斗 找董事会?
I guess fuckin'last ditch, the board?
还有股东?
The shareholders?
好的 杰瑞德想面对面谈
Okay, Jeryd wants face-to-face.
好 也找我吗
Okay. Me, too?
不太可能 我问了
I doubt it. I'm asking
你要不要试试吉尔 或直接找希门尼斯
Do you wanna try Gil or maybe direct to Jimenez?
感觉有点太迫切了 也许先等一天再说
It feels kinda sweaty. Maybe I wait a day
我是说 就是他妈今天了 对吧
A day... I mean, I guess today's the fucking day, right?
今天是冤大头找上门的日子
Like, today's the day the rooster puts its head in our hands
是我们最有筹码的时刻
Today is the moment of maximum leverage
对 看来就只找我
Yep. No, it looks like just me
我们两个人都去有点挤  -叫他去死吧
-It's a bit tight for both of us.   -Fuck him.
好了  -快去...没问题 没问题  -我正要去
All right, go... Sure, sure.   -Going
你那里 有什么结果 再跟我说
Let me know what you come up with
嘿 拉瓦  -嘿 听着
-Hey, Rava.   -Hey, listen.
我们都没事 但是...  -好
-We... We are all okay, but...   -Yeah
心里有点慌
we're a bit freaked out
有辆SUV...
There is an SUV with..
我们觉得有辆SUV...在跟踪我们
Well, we think there's an SUV, and it's... it's following us.
我们可以去办公室吗
So, can we come to the office?
因为 你办公室的安保很好吧
Because you... you have good security at the office
看得到牌照号码吗
What's the license plate?
牌照号码是T3.  -是TR吗 对
The license, it's T... 3, I think.   -Is it T, TR? Right
可能是我的车
'Cause it's probably... it's probably mine.
我不想吓到苏菲 所以就派人去了
I didn't want Sophie to freak, so I just... I just action ed it
你...
Are you? You're..
我的天啊 你派人跟踪我
Oh, my god, you're having me followed?
用秘密监视来表达关心?
This is covert surveillance to show you care?
肯 你在搞什么鬼啊
The actual fuck, Ken?
只是让她和艾弗森多一层保护
Just an extra layer of bubble wrap
你们没事吧 你没事吧
Are you guys okay? You okay?
她也没事吧  -她很害怕 肯
Is she okay?   -She's scared, Ken
我也很害怕  -拉瓦 拉瓦 听着
Okay? I'm... I am scared.   -Rava. Rava, listen.
你就...  -我不知道他们...
Just...   -I don't know what they're...
有地方失火了 有人在恐吓我们
There is... There is shit burning, there is intimidation.
我不懂到底…  -放轻松
I don't understand what's...   -Relax
放轻松 好吗
Okay? Relax.
告诉苏菲 我爱她
Tell Sophie I love her,
我做的一切 都是因为爱她
and that is why I do everything I do
好吗 苏菲
Okay, Soph?
苏菲 我爱你 宝贝
Soph, I love you, sweetie, okay?
不会发生什么事的
Nothing's gonna happen.
出口民调结果是希门尼斯胜选
Exit polls say Jimenez, okay?
我不会让任何人欺负你的 好吗
I won't let the world push you. Okay, sweetie?
好
Okay.
肯
Ken.
嘿 伙计 我只是打来 祝你好运
Hey, man. Just... Just calling to say good luck
数据很不错  -谢了 兄弟
-Great numbers.   -Thanks, man
之前我说话有点冲 我要跟你道歉
And listen, apologies if... if things got a bit heated.
发生太多糟心事了
A lot of shit going down.
胜利巴士和一群烂人在密尔瓦基闹事
Victory vans, his shitheads kicking off in Milwaukee
泛美网科要报道吗  -要 我会去谈的
ATN wanna cover?   -yeah, I'll... talk
但是 得放手让他们去做
but gotta let them do their thing, but yeah
对  -好
Yeah.   -Okay.
听着 丹尼尔在你那里吗
Listen, you got Daniel there?
我看一下
You know, let me... let me see.
请进
Yeah, come in
肯德尔·罗伊找您 您在吗
Sir, you here for Kendall Roy?
嘿 肯德尔  -嘿 丹
-Hey, Kendall.   -Hey, Dan.
嘿 兄弟
Hey, man.
祝你好运
Good luck
我只想说…祝你好运
Good luck. Just... just best of luck
谢了 很高兴跟你聊
Thanks, man. Great to speak
但 大选结束后
But... But when this is over
我们得认真谈谈科技业的事
I think there needs to be a big conversation about tech
我只想说这件事
is all I'd say.
很高兴和你聊 我让纳特来听
Great to speak. I'm gonna put Nate back on
好 还有... 希望 最有能力
Sure, and... may the best man
最能保护美国就业机会
who will, you know, protect American jobs
约束科技业 而且叫做丹尼尔的人赢
and rein in tech and is called Daniel win, you know?
改天再聊 祝你顺心 兄弟
Let's catch up. Have... have a good one, man.
当然 兄弟
Yeah, sure. Sure, man.
今晚 我会在这里盯场
You know, tonight, my eye is just right here
确保一切公平 好吗
making sure it's fair as fuck, all right?
祝你有个愉快的夜晚 兄弟
Have a good night, man.
记得喝水
Stay hydrated.
嘿 快进来,  -好
-Hey. Come on.   -Yeah. Hell yeah
谢谢
Thank you.
好忙哟 你们好
Busy, busy. Hello, hello
瞧你 都快发疯了
Look at you, loss in'it.
像个杀千刀的输家
Like a massive fuckin'loser.
是啊 都怪你
Yeah. Well, I blame you.
连康纳都搞不定
Couldn't deliver Connor, huh?
泛美网科不敢播造假的新闻
ATN scared to run all the fraud.
我从来不插手这些事
Well, I keep my hands out, you know?
去你妈的 你找我干吗 我很忙
Fuck you. What is this?  'Cause, you know, I'm quite busy
你很忙吗  -对 我很忙
You're busy?   -Yes, I am busy.
我又不是骑车四处跑的外卖员
I don't run around town like some fuckin' food bike guy, you know?
我有两件事想说
Just wanted to say a couple things
好
Yeah.
直截了当
Very directly
我们还是觉得有胜算  -当然
-We still think we can win.   -Sure
但是 我现在把心思放在败选上
But I am very focused on losing.
好
All right.
胜选很简单
Winning is easy
赢了就一切水到渠成  -当然
-Winning would take care of itself.   -Sure.
但如果我输了.
But if I lose..
我得琢磨混球所谓的叙事
I need to work on what assholes would call "the narrative."
例如"叛党选战被沿岸自慰工厂
Like "insurgent campaign unfairly maligned as extremist
抹黑成极端主义者”
by the coastal masturbation factories."
没错 如果我败选
Exactly, if I lose,
我要你们正确描述为 虽败犹荣
I want it correctly characterized as a huge victory
表现出人意料之外的好 好吗
Over performed. All right?
我想当总统
I wanna be a president.
希望你能帮我坐上大位
I want you to be a partner in that
如果今晚无法如愿 那就下一次
and if it isn't tonight, it will be next time.
就算你当不了国家总统
" Even if you're not going to be the president
也能当我们的总裁
you're going to be our president."
没错 “你跟我联手 一定可以走得长远
Exactly. " You, me, we'll go far..."
走到对街的酒吧喝酒
" Over the road and into the bar.
听着 今晚可以找个时间谈吗
So, listen, at... at some point tonight, can we do a chat
谈谈我的定位和策略
in terms of the... the "me" of things and, like, how to play it?
因为 马特森对我很差劲
Because Matsson, he treated me quite abominably
但他又好像很信任我
But it felt like trusting
跟我说了很多
and he was saying a lot of things
又很轻松的样子...  -好 好 够了…
and quite relaxed...   -Okay, okay. Enough..
我的咖啡呢
Where's my coffee?
汤姆 我不端咖啡了
Tom, I don't do coffee anymore, man.
不行 格雷格
No, Greg.
格雷格 我必须要头脑清楚 这是一定要的
Greg, I have to be clear. I have to.
如果我昏昏欲睡
If I get drowsy
报错了科罗拉多州的开票结果
and I... mis-call Colorado
马上就天下大乱
Instability, right?
美国失去可信度
And the US loses credibility
中国趁机入侵台湾
China spots an opportunity and invades Taiwan.
用战略性核武器
Tactical nukes.
轰然一声 世界末日来临 大家变回阿米巴原虫
Fuckin' shit goes kablooie and we're back to amoeba
要再演化 得花好多好多年
It's a long way back from pond life
一切只因为 你没有端咖啡给我
cause you failed to get me a double shot, okay?
好 那你...
Okay, well do you...
还要不要 你之前 要求的东西
do you want some of what you asked for?
不用 我不要 你说呢
No, I don't. I don't think so. What do you think?
也许不要 今天是大选之夜
Maybe no. I mean, election night.
不过 你决定吧
Your call. I mean..
好 我要
Yeah, hit me.
不过 这不是正式的
But this is not a... not a thing, okay?
不会被写进书里
It's not going in a book
就…  -好
-Let's just...   -Yeah.
是的 好  -快 快
-Yeah. Okay.   -Quick, quick
快如闪电
Quick as a whistle
这是什么 这个写的是...
What do we have here? What's one the.
白板上写了什么  -白板上
-What's on the board?   -the board?
好的  -这是...
All right.   -There is..
我在擦白板 无辜地擦白板
Just rubbing the board innocently
我只是在擦白板
Simply cleaning the whiteboard here.
好 来吧
Okay. Here we go.
不用 我不要…  -什么
-No... Not for me. No, I...   -What?
经过昨晚 我终于恢复正常了
No, I'm just starting to feel normal from last night
你跟马特森嗑药 但是不跟我?
What? You'll do it with Matsson and not with me?
我才不要整晚被你道德批判 来嘛
I don't want you looking all judgy all night, come on.
不行 我要保持清醒 而且不想上瘾
No, I need a clear head, and I don't wanna get addicted
连续两晚嗑药  -闭嘴 别婆婆妈妈的
-Two nights in a row.   -Shut up, Greg. Don't be Mom.
来嘛  -我不要 拜托
Come on.   -I don't want to. Please.
格雷格 医生说 这对脑子有好处
Greg, it's medically good for your brain?
真的
It is.
难道你觉得阿兹特克人都是笨蛋吗
What are you saying, all Aztecs are stupid?
那是种族歧视
Don't be a racist little bitch about it
快点
Come on.
嗯 好吧  -快点
-Yeah, okay.   -Come on.
不要... 干吗 你在假吸吗
Don't... What? Are you pretending?
不...! 你在假装吸可卡因
-No...   -Are you pretending to do coke?
我有吸一些进去  -快点吸
Some got up.   -Fucking do it.
对嘛 天啊
There. God
很好
Okay.
那是什么鬼  -那个啊
What the fuck is that?   -Oh, that.
他们在点餐
I guess they... they were ordering some for folks.
我叫他们帮你叫一份
I said why not get you one?
酒铺的寿司? 你疯了吗
Bodega sushi? Are you insane?
不是我 是萨姆森
I... No, that's not me. That's Samson
不行 不要萨姆森 格雷格
No, not Samson, Greg!
不要萨姆森 我不要他
Not Samson! Not!
我想要你帮我跑腿
I want you Gregg ing for me
你今晚降职 变回格雷格了
You're busted back down to Greg tonight
不  -是的 今晚
No.   -Yeah, tonight.
我的消化系统是宪法的一部分
My digestive system is basically part of the constitution, okay?
微波加温的牛奶加姜汁
Microwaved milk and ginger shots
美国瓶装水 橄榄油 意大利面 好吗
American bottled water, and spaghetti and olive oil, okay?
好吗  -好啦
-Okay?   -Okay.
好
Okay.
嘿 康
Hey, Con.
汤姆
Tom.
这里有一组人
Yeah, I got this crew here
他们来拍东西
and they're filming the stuff
但拍的东西都没有播出 伙计
but none of it is making it on the show, dude
他们的摄像头里有没有胶卷?
Is there any film in these cameras?
有 我们打算要播出的 康
Yeah, I think we are... we are planning to feature, Con
并没有 因为我一直在看
Well, no. Because I'm watching
我知道 其他电视台不会播
Now, I expected to be frozen out by all those other mooks
但不会连你们都不播吧
but you guys? Come on.
给我一点温暖 兄弟
Give me some sugar, man.
因为 也许大家都投我了
I mean, maybe everyone voted for me.
我们只是不知道
We don't know.
薛定谔的猫
Schrodinger's cat,
薛定谔的猫 汤姆
Schrodinger's cat, Tom.
箱子打开之前...
Until we open the boxes..
我跟另外两个人 一样有可能当总统
I'm just as much president as the other two.
对吧 拜托  -走吧 走吧
Yeah? Come on.   -Let's go, let's go
如果我胜选 那可是世纪大事
If I do it, that's the story of all time.
好 我得挂了
Okay, well, I'll think... I... I've gotta go
但我会想想办法 真的得挂了
But I'll see what I can do. But I've gotta go
因为投票所要关了  -对
'Cause the polls are closing.   -Yeah
如果要发生的话 会发生在肯塔基
Okay, if it's gonna happen anywhere, it's gonna happen in Kentucky
一切都有可能发生
Anything can happen.
万事皆有可能 万事皆有可能
Anything can happen, anything can happen
对
Yeah.
幸亏我没有退选
So glad I didn't drop out.
有参与的话 选举会更有意思
It just makes an election so much more interesting when you're in it
想赢 一定要参与
You gotta be in it to win it.
现在是东岸的七点钟
And it is seven o'clock on the East Coast
表示有六个州已经停止投票了
which means polls have just closed in half a dozen states
此时最受属目的州
The most closely watched states at this hour, Georgia
是有16张选举人票的乔治亚州
with its 16 electoral votes
以及 有13张选举人票的维州
and Virginia with its 13,
这两个 都是很关键的摇摆州
both key battleground states
目前还看不出是谁在两州领先
As of this moment, it is too early to project a winner in either.
我们的选情专家现在可以宣布  -好的
But our decision desk can announce at this hour -Okay.
杰瑞德·门肯众议员
that Representative Jeryd Mencken
会在肯塔基州击败丹尼尔·希门尼斯州长
will defeat Governor Daniel Jimenez in the Commonwealth of Kentucky
同时 也能拿下印第安纳州
as well as in the state of Indiana
门肯在印第安纳州的 选前民调中
where Mencken has enjoyed a lead over Jimenez
就领先了希门尼斯  -好的
-in the pre-election polling.   -Okay
希门尼斯州长将会拿下佛蒙特州
Governor Jimenez will win in the state of Vermont
这是意料中事
no big surprises there,
开票结果将会在今晚前半段宣布
in the early part of the evening
我们要再多收集一些资料 才能预测:
We will need to look at more data before we can make a projection.
嘿 去他的肯塔基 康
Hey. Fuck Kentucky, Con
不要  -要 去他们的
-No.   -Yes, fuck'em
不
No.
我
I...
我不会变成那样 不
I shan't become that. No
可惜 肯塔基没赢 威拉
Alas, Kentucky, Willa
我不能太虚荣
Alas, vanity
选民表达了自己的意见
Voters have made their voices heard
这可能是我们此生最重要的一次选举
This could be the most important election in our lifetime
十四个州即将...  -不用 我说过
-So, with polls about to close...   -No, I told you
你可以给我 比利 谢谢
You can give it to me, Billy, thank you
选情越来越激烈 汤姆
As we heat up, Tom
你要如何...
how much do you wanna give to.
平衡报道恐吓事件
Fair bit of intimidation.
双方人马都有闹事
His folks and ours.
威斯康辛和密尔瓦基的火灾有点难定性
So, like, fire in Wisconsin, in Milwaukee could be nasty
也可能是电线走火 可能是门肯狂粉干的
Could be electrical failure, might be Mencken ists.
摄像头被砸烂 记者在波特兰被骚扰
Camera smashed, crew harassed in Portland
那是他们的人干的  -我信任你
That's the m.   -I trust you.
屏幕有点故障
Again, a little board malfunction here.
他在做什么 怎么了
What's he doing? What's this?
嘿 阿潘 怎么回事  -等一下
-Hey, Pam. What's going on?   -Hold... Hold on.
触控屏,..  -等等 我们在查
The touch... The touch screen.   -Hold on, we're checking it out
触控屏怎么了
What's happening with the touch screen?
叫他不要一直碰触控屏
Tell him to stop touching the touch screen
准备好替换的触控屏,  -触控屏故障了
-We have a replacement in place.   -The touch screen is malfunctioning!
没事 没事  -没事才怪
-It's fine, it's fine.   -Not fine
谁都看得出有事
You can see that it's not fine!
替换的已经拿过去了,  -出故障了 操
-We have a replacement on the way.   -It's malfunctioning! Fuck
触控屏故障了
Touchscreen's malfunctioning
我们要 拉特写
And we're gonna zoom in..
如大家所见 就在这里
Right, as you can see, right here.
屏幕似乎在闹脾气
The board seems to be acting up
触控屏怎么了
What is going on with the touch screen?
触控屏故障了
The touch screen is malfunctioning
怎么了 在搞什么鬼
What... what's going on? What the fuck is going on?
我们在处理
Right, we're on it.
图像生成...搞砸了
A graphics generator, just... It... It shat the bed
什么  -我的触控屏呢
What?   -Where is my touchscreen?
你失控了 戴夫  -在总服务台
Don't, you're losing it, Dave.   -On main desk
在总服务台  -不要失控
On main desk.   -Don't lose it, Dave.
今晚不要失控 戴夫
Don't lose it tonight, Dave.
现在东岸是晚上九点
It is now 9.00pm on the East Coast
好的 触控屏能更换一下吗
Okay, can we get an ETA on that replacement?
汤姆 触控屏是怎么回事
What the fuck's going on with the touch screen, Tom?
我在处理 全都在掌控之中
I'm on it. I'm all over it.
你才没有在处理 快去处理
You're not on it. Fucking get on it
想办法解决
Figure it out.
听到没 马上给我解决
Yeah? Figure it out. Now.
已经在处理了 肯 已经在处理了 他已经…
It's happening. Ken, it's happening. He's already..
我们要接收新的资讯了 格雷格
We're about to get a new batch, Greg
如果收视率下降 我会下去
and if we drop numbers now, I'm gonna come down there
拿你的狗头撞穿触控屏
and put your fucking head through that touchscreen.
已经在弄了,  -快点处理…
-It's all in motion.   -Fix it..
没必要大惊小怪
No need to cat astro phi ze.
触控屏呢 阿潘 要装上去了吗
Where's the touch screen, Pam? Is it loading up?
在装了  -快装上去
It's loaded up.   -Well, get it on air
快把新的装上去 我们会流失观众
Get the new one on air. We're gonna be hemorrhaging.
会成为笑柄
We're gonna be a laughingstock
汤姆 我们在处理了
We're on it, Tom
不会有人注意到的 好吗
No one will notice. Okay?
我们不是第一次了
We've done this before.
有三个屏幕 随时可替换上阵
We have three, and they're all lined up.
没人会注意到吗 我就注意到了
No one will notice? I noticed.
我不是人吗
Am I no one?
我看起来不像人吗
Do I look like no one, huh?
不像吗
Do I?
我们居然会落后社群媒体?
I mean, how the fuck are we behind social media on this?
我们应该领先才对
All right? We need to be leading this
嘿 汤姆  -喂
-Hey, Tom.   -Hello?
威斯康辛发生火灾 你有报道吗
You got this fire in Wisconsin. You... Have you got this?
我想…应该有
Yes, I think we... Yes, I think we have that.
对 是电线走火  -我们为什么没有报道 汤姆
-Yeah. Electrical.   -Why aren't we covering, Tom?
因为 我们要选择 焦点要放在哪里
Well, because we always have to choose what to focus on
失火 不表示就是新闻
and just because something is on fire doesn't make it news.
电线走火  -我们听说不是
Electrical failure?   -Not what we hear.
纳特听说 不是电线走火 汤姆
No, it's... it's not what Nate hears, Tom.
纳特好棒棒哦
Well, bully for Nate.
嘿 汤姆  -嘿 纳特
-Hey, Tom.   -Hey, Nate
我们应该报道这件事 汤姆
We need to be all over this, Tom.
是 我...好
Yeah. I... Okay
我觉得 保持独特观点是很重要的
I just think it's important to... to keep our unique perspective
因为 我们收到互相矛盾的消息
because we are getting conflicting reporting
我手机上的实况照片
What about the actual photos I can see of it happening
又怎么说?
on my fucking phone?
听着 全国现在有很多事情在发生
Look, there are many, many things happening in this nation right now.
有一大堆资料点
There are-a million-data points
我们必须选出其中重要的几个
and we... we have to select the ones that are consequential
如果那些疯子要采取准军事行动 我们就能这么说
If these nutjobs are going paramilitary, we could say that.
对
Yeah.
对 但我们也要尊重观众
Yes, we just need to respect our viewership
不告诉他们 他们不想听的事情 就是尊重?
By not telling them anything they don't wanna hear?
你们有没有听说 反法西斯主义 在密尔瓦基丢燃烧弹的事?
You guys get this about the Antifa firebombing in Milwaukee?
没有 我们听说 是门肯的人干的
Well, we... we hear it's his people, Mencken's.
如果变成新闻事件 我们就报道
Okay, when it becomes a story, then we'll run the story.
这件事情发生在哪里
Well, this is happening in what?
计票中心吗 那...  -对 是新闻
A vote-counting center? So...   -Yeah, it's a story
汤姆 这是个新闻  -我去处理
Tom, it's a story.   -On it.
拜托 不要一直事事都干涉我  -汤姆?
-Do not micromanage me, please.   -Tom?
什么事  -他们在疏散了
-Yes, yes.   -Tom, they're evacuating
我们在当地派直升机升空 和一名记者出动
We've got a local chopper up and a reporter on the way
各位 我要去处理这事了
Okay. Guys, I've got To manage this
有什么事情 我随时报告
I'm gonna... But, I mean, I'll keep you looped, yeah?
你们跟格雷格说 好吗
Talk to Greg, yeah?
好 嘿 嘿
Yeah. Hey, hey.
我很乐意 跟各位报告最新进展
Happy to keep you fully abreast here.
我们不要跟格雷格说话  -我可以帮你们传话
We're not talking to Greg.   -I can be your link up guy
不要 搞什么鬼
No. What the fuck?
楼下完全是外行当道
Amateur hour down there
如果发生在密尔瓦基 而且是蓄意的
Okay, so, if it happened in Milwaukee and if it's deliberate
那肯定是门肯派的人干的
then it's Mencken ists
可能是栽脏
False flag. Could be.
你不能一直说栽账
You can't just say "false flag'
只因为...   -栽赃
-every time you don't...   -False flag
听到自己不认同的事情  -栽赃
-fucking agree with something.   -False flag.
两位
Okay, guys.
为各位报道密尔瓦基火灾事件
We wanna report about a fire in Milwaukee
原本以为只是电线走火
initially thought to have been caused by an electrical failure.
但现在 出现许多诉求和反诉求
But now there are claims and some counterclaims
提出者为 几个
being made by groups who were protesting
抗议选举违规的组织...  -嘿
-alleged voting irregularities...   -Hey
你知道有没有选票没受损的?
Okay, well, do you know if any of the ballots are intact?
看样子不太可能
It doesn't look likely
你在哪里
Where are you at?
要看损失了多少选票
Depends how many votes have gone
但是 有选票受损了?  -对
But ballots have been lost?   -Oh, yeah.
我们要包机去密尔瓦基
We're chartering flights to milwaukee.
我们的分析团队做了大量的计算
A ton of number-crunching by our analytics team
我们试着核对密尔瓦基的选举人名册
We're trying to check the Milwaukee County voter rolls
看哪些人已经投过票了
to see who's voted so far, but..
在叙事上 你可以帮我们吗
Listen, can you help with the narrative?
可以
Oh, yeah.
你人手够吗
Okay, well, have you got all the bodies that you need?
够 我们人手够了
Yeah. Yeah, we have bodies.
我们有一个霹雳小组
We have a SWAT team on it
他们正在跟密尔瓦基的团队交接
They're interfacing with the Wisconsin team
显然 他碰得太用力了
Apparently, he's just touching too hard
格雷格
Greg.
什么  -显然他碰得太用力了...
What?   -He's touching way...
什么 不行 罗曼
What? No. Rome.
罗曼 高层不可以下来
Roman, no brass on the battlefield, okay?
那是洛根的日内瓦公约规定
That's one of Logan's Geneva Conventions
拜托 拜托  -我只是来看一下怎么回事
-Please, please.   -Just a pop-in. What's going on?
计票中心疏散了吗
They evacuated the count center?
我不知道
No, I don't know.
我又少了一个触控屏
I've just lost another touchscreen.
现在只剩下他妈最后一个了
I'm down Tomy last fucking touchscreen.
怎么了  -没什么
What's going on?   -Oh, nothing.
汤姆觉得 中国在侵入他的设备
Tom just thinks that China's hacking his tech.
我没有 但我觉得 你们待在楼上会比较舒服
I do not, but I do think you would be more comfortable upstairs.
格雷格 拜托你...
Greg, will you please.
拜托你带他们上楼  -好
-Will you please help them upstairs?   -Oh, yes.
你们在楼上会比较舒服 拜托
I think you will be comfortable upstairs
请让我带领...  -你好 汤姆
-Do we mind if what?   -Hello? Tom
你好 西沃恩  -我可以带领你们
-Hello, Siobhan.   --Can I just wrangle you...
带领? 别一直说“带领”  -那里还有选票吗
"Wrangle? " Stop saying "wrangle." -Were the ballots still in there?
现在是怎样  -怎么回事
Okay. Where... Where are we?   -What's going on?
汤姆 可以解释给我们听吗  -格雷格 请你带贵宾们
-Tom, can you catch us up?   -Greg, can you please take the VIPs
到楼上去  -好
to upstairs setting?   -Yes
好 我带你们三位...  -格雷格 我能不能.
-Can I grab the three of you and...   -Greg, can I.
汤姆 记者在路上  -怎么了
-Tom. Reporter on the way.   -Yes?
四分钟后到  -知道了 好的 好的
-Three, four out.   -Okay. All right, all right
汤姆  -什么事
-Tom?   -Yes?
可以...可以借一步说话吗
Can I... Can I have a word?
真的假的  -很快就说完了 汤姆
Really?   -Won't take long, Tom.
我真的没时间  -我知道 先让我…
-I really can't.   -I know, but just let me..
好 我只想
Okay, I just...
可以听我说吗
Can you please?
我想为昨晚
I just wanted to apologize
说的一些话道歉
for some of the things that I said last night, okay?
好 好
Okay, okay.
而且 给你一个机会...
And to... you know, give you an opportunity to..
看你这个表情 我说不下去
Well, I can't do it to that, so..
那我应该用什么表情
How should I frame my face?
你担心我会把你跟马特森的事说出去?
Are you scared that I'm gonna blab about you and Matsson?
我父亲才刚过世 好吗
My father just died, yeah? My..
我父亲才刚过世,  -对
Like, my father just died.   -Yeah
也许 你可以在那件事上对我体贴一点
So, maybe, you know, I can get a little consideration on that
还有 我最近因为各种原因 状况不佳
and for, you know, a number of reasons I've been feeling off-kilter,
对不起 但是
So I'm sorry, but..
能不能稍微...  -没问题 没问题
could I get a modicum of?   -Sure, sure.
那是什么意思  -没问题
What does that mean?   -Sure.
没问题?  -这表示 你恨他 西沃恩
-" Sure?" -It means you hated him, Siobhan.
我不恨他 我爱他
didn't hate him. I love him
你们的关系很复杂
Well, it was complicated
但有时候 你真的很恨他
but sometimes, you certainly hated him
还有...你也算是害死了他
and... and you also sorta killed him
你说什...  -算是...
What the...   -Sort of.
算是
Sort of.
这部分我一定会记住
That's the part that I'm gonna remember.
谢了 太感谢你了
Thanks. No, thank you. Thanks. No, thank you
你知道吗 其实我还怀孕了
Okay, you know what? Actually, also, I'm pregnant
对 怀了你的孩子
Yeah. By you.
我找不到好时机告诉你
And there's... never a good time to say
但是 你必须知道 所以 好
but you need to know, so okay
现在你知道了  -明白
-Now you know.   -Right
是…
It's
是真的吗
That even true?
什么
What?
你是真的怀孕了吗
Like, is that even true?
还是说 你的新手法 或战术?
Or is that, like, a new position or a tactic?
或是什么…
Or what? What?
好吧
Okay
我们有个区域
We... So, we have an area.
我想...是不是在楼上
I guess we... Is it the upstairs?
这边  -你还好吗
Yeah, this way.   -Are you okay?
是的 还好 我
Yeah. Yep. I'm...
我觉得 现在的情况很棘手…
Look, I think things are tough.
我跟汤姆的关系 但...
with... with my situation and Tom, but
要不要我们派人去干掉他
You want us to have him killed?
我们可以帮你  -好 也许吧 我...
-I could do that.   -Yeah, may be. I.
他只是...
I mean, I think, you know, he's just..
他只是渣男
He's just a piece of filth
我有些事 想告诉你们 但是...
and there's stuff I would like to tell you, but I.
嘿 我一直想叫他们离开
Hey, I've been trying to get them Tomove
不是轰他们走 但是...如果
not in a aggressive way, but... if..
总之 不要信任他
Yeah, I mean, you just can't trust him
知道 放心吧
Yeah. We got you.
大火还在熊熊燃烧  -谢了
-In terms of the fire, it is still burning -Thanks
消防队控制火势已经很吃力 更别说扑灭了
and crews are struggling to contain, let alone extinguish.
有没有传出伤亡?
Are there any reports, so far, of injuries?
幸亏目前还没有
None for now, fortunately.
中心已经立即疏散
The building was evacuated immediately
所有人员都撤离了
and all workers have been accounted for
既然大家都在这里 我就到里边去
Well, I'm gonna sneak, now that we're all in here.
罪魁祸首是谁
Who's responsible?
这才是新闻吧
That’s the story, right?
纵火的是什么人
Who burnt this place down?
我觉得 这种事 总有几个热门人选
Tome, it always comes down to a couple old favorites
黑人 或是犹太人
The blacks or the Jews.
闹你们的 我在开玩笑  -拜托一下 好吗
I'm kidding. It's a fuckin'joke.   -Would you please? Please?
知道了  -好
Got it.   -All right, here.
小西 请跟我来  -嘿 康纳
-Shiv, just follow me. Follow me.   -Hey, Connor.
罗曼
Rome.
罗曼 杰瑞德不接电话
Jeryd isn't picking up
也难怪 他今晚很忙的
Yeah, I... I wonder if it's a busy night for him
我在想 之前的提议还有效吗
Because I wondered if what we talked about might still be on offer.
让我做大使的提议
Ambassador ship-wise?
那是昨天的提议 康纳
Yeah, well, that was kind of a yesterday offer, Connor.
如果他这次败选
You know if he doesn't make this
你得负一部分责任
you're gonna be partially fucking responsible
希望你可以接受  -罗曼...
-Hope you're cool with that.   -Rome...
我为了竞选 花了差不多一亿了
I've spent, like, a hundred mill here.
我连鸟地方都去不成吗
Couldn't I get a sniff of even a little guy?
去秘鲁推动政变?
Organize a little coup down in old Peru?
或是让我坐车去塔吉克?
Put me in a van to Tajikistan?
不能让我去乌拉圭享享福吗?
Couldn't I just be our fun guy in Uruguay?
你的押韵很有趣 但这 对他有什么好处 康?
Your rhymes are compelling, but what's in it for him, Con?
也许是 这个世代最杰出的政治人物
Oh, maybe just one of the finest political operators
帮他做事?
of his generation sorting shit out?
好 我再打给你
Okay, yeah. I'll... I'll get back to you.
在这里
Just this one
其实是 每隔四年
Yeah, every four years, in fact.
可能要取决于几个州
It's probably going to come down to a handful of states
例如 威斯康辛 俄亥俄
I ike Wisconsin, Ohio.
宾州 乔治亚 和亚利桑那
Pennsylvania, Georgia, and Arizona.
不要管初期的情况
Ignore the narratives early on
做好心理准备
and just realize that
即将发生缠斗 最后那几个州
that we're going to be in for a dogfight for late night
今晚将会是长夜漫漫
in those last couple of states
东岸现在是晚上11点
It is 11.00pm on the East Coast.
又有四个关键州的投票截止了
Polls have just closed in four more key states.
好 谢谢  -泛美网科的选情专家
Okay, thanks.   -The ATN Decision Desk
现在可以预测 丹尼尔…
can now project that Daniel
州法规定 邮寄选票计算完毕
So, under state law, the vote can't be certified
选举结果才能经过认证
until the absentee ballots are counted
所以 威斯康辛州的选举结果
So, no Wisconsin result is valid
要等邮寄选票计算完毕才算有效
until the absentee ballots are counted
好的 丹尼尔觉得如何
Okay. And how does Daniel feel?
很有把握 但是也很害怕
Confident, but terrified
我不知道 这种感觉有没有名字
I don't know. Is the re a... Is there a name for that feeling?
“信恐“吗
" Cuspy "?
罗曼 根据威斯康辛州法计票...
Rome, so under Wisconsin law, the vote can't be certified.
门肯说结束了 威斯康辛结束了
Mencken says we're done. Wisconsin's done.
这是他们的立场  -不对
That's their position.   -But, well, no.
现在密尔瓦基少了10万张邮寄选票
There's, like, 100,000 absentee Milwaukee ballots missing
知道这个信息后 我们得想个
So, we have to figure out a way to go forward.
着手的方法  -怎么着手 破坏门肯领先的幅度吗
-knowing that information.   -Go forward? To undermine Mencken's lead?
他领先了吗
Does he have a lead?
是这样吗  -对 是的
-I mean, is... is that right?   -Yep. Yes
那是人为的领先
An artificial lead.
因为密尔瓦基少了十万张邮寄选票
With 100,000 Milwaukee absentee ballots missing
每一张选票都要被算到才行
Every vote must be counted
我觉得她说得对  -什么
-I think she's right.   -What?
我觉得她说得对  -对 好吧
I think she's right there.   -Well... Well, yeah, okay
但 我们可以计算现有的选票
But we... we can count the votes that we have.
虽然很不幸地 有一些不见了
However, unfortunately, some are lost, so...
"很不幸的 有一些不见了?"
" Unfortunately, some are lost "?
意思是 被法西斯混蛋放火烧了
Meaning what? Fascist fuck heads burnt them.
这我们无法确定
We literally do not know that.
也可能是你的那批混蛋 他们最爱放火
It could very easily be your fucks. They love fires
你在为 潜在的暴力 制造机会
You're making hay from political violence.
或是 你的人 自知输定了
Or your guys knew they were going to lose
所以 做出疯狂之举 让外界质疑举选结果
so they did something crazy to throw it into question
重新投票  -你不是真的这么觉得吧
-and get a revote.   -You don't believe that
也许是 我不知道
Yeah, maybe I do. I don't know.
希门尼斯会赢得宾州 密歇根 和亚利桑那
Okay, well, Jimenez is gonna take Pennsylvania, Michigan, and Arizona
我不知道你为什么要盛气凌人
so I don't know why you're getting so fucking uppity about this shit
你这么有把握 又为什么要盛气凌人
Why are you getting so uppity about this shit if you're so confident?
因为 如果门肯赢了 会是世界末日
Because if Mencken wins, it's the end of the world, okay?
我希望能有点他妈的缓冲
So, I'd like a little fucking cushion.
希门尼斯不会阻挡Go Jo的交易
Jimenez won't block the Go Jo deal,
所以 就让他去死吧 对吗
so fuck the guy, right?
谁说得准 也许他会
Well, who knows? Maybe he would.
我们不能让那成为决定因素
And that's not... You can not let that be the thing that's..
那不是决定因素吧 肯
That's not the thing, right? Ken?
肯  -我不知道
-Ken.   -I don't know.
不要 别这么愤世嫉俗
No, don't... don't get cynical.
我不是...愤世嫉俗 我就是…
It's not... not cynical. No, it's just..
事情都发生了
What's happening is happening
我很实际  -是啊
-I'm a realist.   -Oh, yeah.
你这人会割断儿子的喉咙
Says the man who'd cut his son's throat
在山路上吃了他
and the n eat him on the high pass
FVA说 回报的票数够多 可以决定威斯康辛的结果了
Hey, so FVA is saying they have enough vote reported to call Wisconsin
所以 美国自由之声 和瓦利新闻 要宣布了
So, Freedom Voice America and Vera News are calling it
好极了 那群疯子
Great, the maniacs.
我们不能输 一定要快
Well, can't get outflanked, and we need to be fast
我们也该宣布 对吧
so I think we should call it, right?
等等 等一下 等一下  -不要...
-Wait, hold on, hold on.   -No..
汤姆 独立的...
Tom, what... what is, like, an independent?
可以帮我们请选情专家达温过来吗
Can... Can you get us Decision Desk Darwin?
是的 好
Yes. Yep.
我想针对密尔瓦基的情况 说几句话
I want to say a few words about the emerging situation in Milwaukee.
美国人民正高度关切的情况
A situation the American people are watching with increasing concern
选举有个既定的过程 这…
We have a process, and it is..
要尊重过程 每张票都要算到
" Respect the process. Count every vote."
这家伙真的有够无聊
He's so fucking dull.
掏出你的老二 打个手枪 随便做点什么事
Flop your dick out. Pop a nut. Do something
我们知道 如果没有计算所有选票
That decision will have no legitimacy
决定就不具法律效力
if it does not account for all the ballots cast.
好的 达温 谢谢
Okay, Dar. Thank you.
达温 谢谢 我们有一些想法和问题
And we have some thoughts and some questions. And.
谢谢你 达温 你有威斯康辛目前的结果吗
Thank you, Darwin. Do you have a result as it stands in Wisconsin?
我们计算了目前的选票
We've tallied the vote totals so far.
我知道 然后呢
Yeah, I know. And?
门肯大幅领先 会造成影响的
The margin for Mencken is significant
不是还没算到的选票
Couldn't be made up by outstanding existing uncounted votes.
而是消失的那一批
Only the ones destroyed
好的 我们不能等被烧掉的选票 宣布吧
Okay, and we're not waiting for burned votes, so we call it.
不行 我觉得...  -对吗
-No, I... I think...   -Right?
我觉得 应该重新来过
I think they have to hold it again.
不是吗 重新投票
No? Like, a revote
我觉得重新投票很少见 也非常复杂
I would say re vote is incredibly rare and complex
我们理论上虽然知道
because while we theoretically know
哪些人要求要邮寄选票
everyone who requested an absentee ballot
但是 不确定到底多少人把选票寄回来了
we don't entirely know how many turned them in
而且 威斯康辛的法律并没有规定该怎么做 所以...
and there's nothing in Wisconsin law that really covers what to do, so..
说得对 所以 不能重新投票 门肯赢了 谢谢
Exactly. You can't do it. Boom, Mencken. Thank you.
但是 我们觉得...团队知道
But, of course, we think... we... the team knows.
我们知道 被烧掉的选票 大概是投给谁的
we know how the missing votes would have broken down.
选票不见了
Well, they're gone.
没人知道是投给谁的
There's no way to know what was on those ballots
我们知道 根据过去的结果
Well, we... we do know because past elections
密尔瓦基向来是压倒性地投给民主党的
Milwaukee overwhelmingly votes Democrat.
但是 你并不是确切知道  -当然
But you don't actually know.   -Sure
但 基本上是知道的  -我们确实知道
I just, basically, do know.   -We do know.
因为你很接地气
Because you're so plugged in,
所以知道那些农夫的想法
you know how the little peasants vote
知道他们投给谁 你根本不知道
what's in their hearts, 'cause you don't know.
罗曼 拜托 大人在说话 你别闹
Rome, Come on. This is the grown-ups 'table. Be serious
我没有闹
This is serious.
每次选举都有选票不见
This is serious. Ballots get lost every election.
烧掉的选票找不回来了
You can't get burnt ballots back
听你放屁
Bullshit. Just bullshit.
放屁…  -你才在放屁
Bullshit...   -It's not bullshit
你满嘴屁话  -小西
-Full of fucking bullshit.   -Shiv.
小西  -干吗
Shiv.   -What?
你听起来有点崩溃  -汤姆 你他妈给我小心点
-You sound a little unhinged.   -You fucking watch it, Tom.
我们真的知道  -好的 好的
-We do know.   -Okay, okay.
我们不可能知道选民投给谁
There's no way to say in here how people would have voted
难道 你跑跑模型 就可以不管选民了吗
I mean, you wanna just run your model and not bother with all the people?
我们是说 按往例 选民大多投给…
We're saying. historically, people overwhelmingly
以前 人们还火烧女巫呢
Historically, people used to burn witches.
你是说 我们也该照做吗  -怎么说到火烧女巫了
Are you saying we should do that?   -What the fuck? Burn witches?
罗曼 听好
Rome, look,
我们就是知道 那把火烧了
we just know that the fire would have destroyed
很多希门尼斯的票
a lot of Jimenez ballots.
所以 是爱放火的共和党拿下疯狂女巫
Oh, so fire favors GOP, claims mad witch
我们就是知道  -好的
We just know.   -Okay
选举不能重来
Well, we're not gonna rerun the election
若右派被冤枉 有什么影响吗
and if the right gets wrongly blamed for this, what would that do?
如果是左派呢 场面会变得很难看
If the left does? Could get nasty
你要去哪里
Where are you going?
我要去上大号
I am going to the bathroom to shit.
你要我开直播吗
Would you like me to live stream it?
肯 你说呢
Ken, you wanna weigh in?
我只是觉得好难  -我们知道
-I just think it's hard.   -But we know.
我们就是知道
We just do.
选票若没有被烧掉 希门尼斯一定会拿下这个州
That if the lost votes were counted, Jimenez would take the state
马克在直接评论 泛美网科之声
Mark is commenting directly, ATN voice.
职业政客不断地拿出来说.
...national politicos who, time after time, come up with
这很好笑吧
isn't this funny.
支持传统价值观的选票没有列入计算
with polls which under-count support for traditional values
也许有些疯子 听说他们表现不如预期
So, yeah, maybe some of the crazies heard they were underperforming
决定阻止计票 毁灭证据
and decided to stop the counting and destroy the evidence.
所以 没错 请紧闭尊口
And so, yeah, you just stay quiet.
罗曼送谈话要点来了
Roman sent talking points
我们来猜 那些选票是投给谁的
We'll guess what we think was on those ballots.
然后来决定投票结果 好吗
We'll decide, yeah?
他在下面吗
Is he down there?
他们最清楚了 对吗
They know best, right?
你们就乖乖吃晚餐
And you'll eat what's for dinner
因为 他们不喜欢 会顶嘴
because they don't really care for folks who answer back
或 问太多问题的人
or ask too many questions.
闭嘴 不懂科学的社会渣滓
Shut up. In numerate residuum.
我们会搞清楚的
We'll figure it out
给你指派新的政府 大摇大摆地闯进你家
and issue you with your new government to march into your homes
随心所欲地夺走你们的自保机制
and take whatever we want in the way of your mechanisms of self-defense
告诉原本是你女儿的儿子
and tell your son she's actually your daughter
或是原本是儿子的女儿
or the other way around, and then.
嘿 小西 你可以不要过去吗
Hey, Shiv, do you mind actually not going on the floor?
小西
Shiv?
新任总统将向他的朋友们开放边界
And the new president is opening up his borders to his friends
狗屁 狗屁 罗曼 你去死吧
Bullshit. Bullshit, Roman. Fuck you
很明显
It's obvious, painful
我们必须要 更聪明 更好
We need to be smarter than this, better than this
我们需要反面观点
We need a fucking opposing viewpoint
可以叫保安来吗
Would you call security?
抱歉 你不能下来 这不是我的意思 是规定
Sorry, you can't come down here. It's... It's not me. It's just.
嘿 卢卡斯
Hey, Lukas.
这他妈是怎么回事
What the fuck is going on?
是啊 这是个好问题
Yeah. Great fucking question.
很震撼的评论吧
Powerful commentary, huh?
罗曼 我觉得这样不太好
I don't feel good necessarily about this, Rome
真是的
Shucks.
没问题吗 我要动起来吗
Is it okay? Do I need to hustle?
要准备好 跟恐怖先生相处吗
Do I need to get ready to be cozy with this fucking Mr. Scary here?
不用 我能处理的
No. No, I can handle. I can handle it
因为 格雷格说 情况有点吓人
Yeah,'cause Greg tells me it's getting kinda hairy in there.
别让他们弄坏我的玩具 小西
Don't let them break my toy, Shiv, okay?
不会的 你放心 再联络  -好 明白
No. All good. I'll be in touch.   -Yeah. Got you
抱歉 请你离开这个楼层 可以吗
Sorry, we just need you off the floor, if that's okay
没问题 有空吗
Yeah. Got a minute?
显然 民主党在指控这场火灾有偏见
And now, apparently the Democrats are accusing this fire of being biased
没错 对
That's right. Yeah
这听起来很像他们的作风
That sounds pretty much something out of their camp.
这场火 只烧了民主党的选票
It only burnt Democratic votes
这是那种很挑剔的火
Yeah, you know, it's one of those... it's one of those picky fires.
进来  -好
Come on in.   -Yeah
那么...  -我只想关心你的情况
So...   -Yeah, just wanted to check in.
今天好忙 所以…
You know? It's been busy, so.
对啊 今天是大选之日
Right. Yeah, on election day.
对 对
Yeah, yeah.
你昨晚跟卢卡斯过得如何
So, how was your night last night with Lukas?
小西 我跟他去喝酒
Shiv, I... I went for a drink with them.
那不是我的错
That... That's not my fault
格雷格瑞 你觉得我迷人吗
Do you find me attractive, Gregory?
我不会去想那种事情
I don't think of things such as that
我以为你是恶心兄弟之一
Oh, I thought you were a disgusting brother
还是 你觉得 太恶心了?
Is that... Oh, was that too disgusting for you?
这很不恰当
This is not appropriate.
对 很抱歉
Yeah, I... I'm sorry.
因为 我只是想让你知道...
Cause I'm just letting you know...
如果你想搞我...
that if you try to fuck me.
我会杀了你
I'll kill you
收到
Got it.
我知道了 抱歉
Got it. Sorry. Yeah.
我唯一的问题是…
I guess my... my only question..
如果你跟他之间有什么结果...
would be if... if anything did come to pass... in terms of you and he..
你知道的 沉默是金
you know, silence is golden
但是 有多金?
Like, how golden?
你有什么提议吗
Is there an offer?
有
Yeah
我的提议是 让你四肢健全
How about I offer for you to keep all your internal organs on your insides
而不是被我开肠破肚
rather than I pull them out your ass hole?
去吧 傻大个
Go on. You're lumber.
眼睛擦亮点
Keep your snout out.
同时 无所不用其极地 摧毁不同的意见
Simultaneously destroying diversity of opinion wherever possible
嘿 你猜怎么着
Hey, guess what?
门肯会阻止交易
Mencken will block the deal
他会让交易胎死腹中
Straight up. He'll kill it.
如果他胜选 会把交易送交联邦贸易委员会什么的
If he wins, he'll refer to FTC, whatever.
订一条新法律 禁止外国人持有
New law, foreign ownership tightening
总之 他会让交易告吹
Whatever. He'll screw it up
交换条件是 我们今晚支持他
In exchange for our support tonight
他有明讲吗
In, like, in so many words? Or?
我一字不漏地转述了
In those words
要我叫汤姆来吗
Shall I get Tom?
叫我们的人形算盘来吗
Shall I get the human abacus?
要不要? 来吧
Shall I? Let's do it.
这是好消息
This is good news.
嘿,  -谢谢你的...
Hey.   -So, thanks for whatever.
我们的票数够了 所以...
We have the votes, so..
没有办法公平地重选
Can't rerun fairly
也不能让左派恐怖分子影响我们
and can't let lefty terrorism affect us
我们就 宣布结果吧
So let's call it.
有什么先例?
On what precedent?
凭谁的权力?
By... By what authority?
凭我的权力 韦斯达的CEO
By the power of me, the CEO of Waystar
叫你命令主播 宣布结果
telling you what to put on the telly-box mouth people.
各位 我认为 我们不能这么做
I don't think we can do that, guys
我觉得我们可以 阿达
I think we can do it, Dar.
如果我们宣布了 其他人又支持他...
If we call it and the... the others went his way..
还有一些州的结果没有出来
Right, well, look, there are still outstanding states.
密歇根 俄亥俄 乔治亚 亚利桑那
There's Michigan, Ohio, Georgia, Arizona.
真的没什么大不了 才一个州而已
It's really not that big a deal. It's one state.
我担心这个决定 我没有办法...
I'm worried it's not a decision that I could necessarily.
好 谢谢你
Yeah, thank you,
达温 大家都很尊重你
and everyone respects you, Darwin
但 这不是数字问题
but this isn't actually a numbers thing
威斯康辛和密尔瓦基的选委会
I mean, the Wisconsin Elections Commission
会告上法庭
the Milwaukee Election Commission will go to court
选举阵营也会提起诉讼
and the camps will litigate it
到时 门肯也能左右管辖权之争
and it'll be a jurisdiction fight that I think Mencken might shake
但 你知道 我…
but, you know, I..
我们不能...我不能...  -很好
-We can't... I can't just...   -Yeah. That's... That's great.
但我觉得没问题 有事我负责
But I'm just gonna say we're good and that's on me.
现有的选票已经计算完毕
The votes that exist have been tallied
本州 由门肯胜选
and that gives Mencken the state
这 轮不到你决定
But you don't... you don't make the call
要由我来决定
make the call
我们一起决定
We're gonna make the call together, Tom
在我决定之前 你不能决定
You can't make the call until I make the call
好的 我不会逼你
Okay, so I'm... And I'm not gonna make you do anything
但  威斯康辛的情况就是这样
This is the situation in Wisconsin
不如就非正式地宣布
How would you feel if we were to... not "call it " call it, but..
我们可以说 悬而未决
Like, pending. We could call it pending.
你甚至可以解释
You could even explain it.
我们可以让你在镜头前解释
We can get a camera on you to explain it to people.
我是可以解释
I could explain.
可不可以加图表 清楚表明
And could there be a graphic that makes it clear
这不是正式的结果
the call isn't... a "call " call?
而是悬而未决
Pending call.
抱歉
Sorry.
好 所以...  -可以了吗
All right, so...   -Yeah?
满意了吗 老混蛋们  -可以了
Satisfied, fucky fucks?   -Okay
当然可以  -很好
-Sure we can.   -Great.
怎么了
What's up?
你还好吗 怎样
You okay? What?
我眼睛进东西了
There's something in my eyes.
格雷格 嘿  -芥末
Greg. Hey.   -Wasabi.
是芥末吗
Is it wasabi?
我眼睛进芥末了?
There's wasabi in my eyes?
老天  -我眼睛进芥末了吗
Oh, Jesus.   -I've got wasabi in my eyes?
等一下...稍等
Oh, wait... Hold on.
来  -进去更多了
-Here.   -No, it's gone more in.
进更多了
It's gone more in
怎么回事  -我手上有芥末
-What's going on?   -It's on my fingers.
我手上有芥末  -你还好吗
It's on my fingers.   -Are you okay?
你们把他怎么了  -好疼
What did you do to him?   -It stings.
快去拿水 格雷格
Get some water or something, Greg
我的妈呀 天啊
Holy mother, mother of God
杀了我吧 痛死了
fuck me slowly, this smarts!
好了 格雷格  -用水冲冲
-Okay, Greg...   -Put... Put water in it.
用水冲冲
Put... Put water in
是芥末...  -这是柠檬水 格雷格
It's was a bi...   -That's lemon! It's lemon, Greg
是原味气泡水  -天啊 我操
-That's clear! It's La Croix!  -Jesus! Fuck!
格雷格 你在做什么  -有柠檬味
Greg, what are you doing?   -It's lemony
有柠檬味  -我的天啊
-It's lemony! -Jesus H. Christ!
不对 这是天然的 是医疗用的
No, it's natural, like medical.
给我 我的天啊
Give it to me. Oh, my gosh
柠檬味不明显 只有一丝酸味
It's not that lemony. It's just a hint of lemon.
达温 可以宣布了吗
Darwin? You good to call it?
罗曼 他不能宣布
He can't fucking call it, Rome.
我们要宣布 小西 他刚刚宣布了
We're calling it, Shiv. He just called it.
很好  -好吗
-Great.   -Okay?
格雷格 不要再把柠檬水或芥末放进他的眼睛
Greg, do not put any more lemon water or wasabi in his eyes
行吗
Okay?
你还好吗  -很好
-Do we look okay?   -Yeah.
嘿 康 你不该来这里
Hey, Con. You shouldn't really be in here
也祝你晚安
And a very good evening to you, too.
嘿 总统先生  -罗曼
Hey, Presidente.   -Rome.
亲爱的...等一下
Sweetheart... One sec.
在这里等我一下 好吗 宝贝
Would you wait over here for me a second, baby?
各位 在这里等我一下
Fellas, would you wait over here for me a second?
什么事  -罗曼 我有个主意
-Yeah, yeah?   -Rome. One thought
如果 我对着他承认败选呢?
How about I concede in his direction?
我帮他 他也帮我
scratch his balls, he scratches mine?
有意思 也许可以
That's interesting. Perhaps-ish
我问一下
Let me check on that. Yeah
也许可以吗  -对 也许可以
Perhaps-ish?   -Perhaps-ish, yeah
跟我来  -我来了
Come on.   -I'm coming.
阿潘 我们要宣布
Pam, we're calling
门肯赢得威斯康辛 把图像准备好
Wisconsin for Mencken. Get the graphics up
戴夫 跟他们说 我们五分钟后要宣布威州的结果
Dave, let them know we're five out from calling Wisconsin
好 我们五分钟后宣布 门肯在威斯康辛胜选
All right, we are calling Wisconsin for Mencken, five minutes
图像准备好了吗
Is that graphic ready?
现在有重要结果要宣布
There is a big ol'call to make right now
那就是 泛美网科预测 杰瑞德·门肯
and that is ATN is projecting that Jeryd Mencken
在威斯康辛胜选
has won the state of Wisconsin
我们报道了密尔瓦基计票中心的火灾
You know, we've been reporting on that fire in the Milwaukee vote count center.
尽管如此 我们的选情专家有把握可以宣布结果了
Nonetheless, our decision desk is confident in making this call
杰瑞德·门肯 拿下威斯康辛
Jeryd Mencken has won the state of Wisconsin
蓝色长城正式倒塌
and there goes the Blue Wall
一共10张选举人票
That's ten electoral votes
让门肯的总票数达到246张.
That brings Mencken up to 246.
好了 兄弟 好了 有搞头了
Okay, man. Okay. There's something there
见不得光的后座肮脏交易
Sordid back seat fuck job.
细说
Oh, tell me more.
他想要维持这股气势  -杰瑞德·门肯
-He wants to keep up the momentum.   -Jeryd Mencken is now
现在只差24张选举人票 就当选总统了
24 electoral votes away from winning the presidency
你真的想要吗
Do you really want it?
斯洛文尼亚啊 威拉
Slovenia, Willa
我很挣扎 他是个大右派
I mean, I am torn, and he's very right wing
但是...
But...
到维也纳吃午餐 到威尼斯吃晚餐
Vienna for lunch, Venice for dinner..
在杜布罗夫尼克吃早餐
And Dubrovnik for breakfast
同胞们 今晚的情势已经明朗了
My fellow Americans, it's becoming clear tonight that as far as we can tell
杰瑞德·门肯先生 应该会是
that as far as we can tell, Mr. Jeryd Mencken will likely be
下一届的美国总统
the next president of the United States
对  -我祝他一切顺利
Yes.   -And I, for one, wish him well
康纳有出来选总统哦?
Connor was running for president?
虽然 我规划了明确良好的施政路线.
For although I set out a clear and compelling path.
好啦  -但 美国人 以无上的智慧
Okay. All right.   -America, in her divine wisdom
选择了另一条路线
has chosen to take another.
祝大家好运
Well, good luck
我想跟我的第一个竞选搭档说…
And I'd like to say, Tomy first running mate
在这里就不提那个人的名字了
who I will not dignify with a name-check
如果那个女人没有退出
but had that woman not dropped out
如果我没有找另一个
and then had I not had to replace her with another figure
扶不起的阿斗 来取代她
who turned out not to be able to bear the weight of public scrutiny
如果我没有 被这两个...小丑背叛
had I not been betrayed by those two... jackrabbits
天晓得结果会是怎样
who knows?
嫉妒政治 是很丑陋的游戏
Politics of envy. Ugly game.
我碰巧是个亿万富翁
I happen to be a billionaire
很抱歉
Sorry.
但是 说老实话 美国 这次你们搞砸了
But honestly, America, you flunked it
看来你们得另外找个没钱的蠢货
I guess you're gonna have to find some other poor mook's paps
来吃奶  -好的
to suck le on.   -Okay.
腐败两党制度的丧尸
The corrupt bipartisan system zombie
好  -将继续前进
All right.   -marches on.
今晚 我要告诉我的朋友
And so, I call out to my friends tonight
和支持者
to my people
康迷们 我向你们致敬
I say, Con heads, I salute you.
美国 你们最好提心吊胆…
And America, be afraid.
因为 我警告过你们…
be warned..
康迷会卷土重来的
for the Con heads are coming
谢谢 天佑美国
Thank you. God bless America
泛美网科的选情专家 现在预测 丹尼尔·希门尼斯
ATN Decision Desk is now projecting Daniel Jimenez
击败杰瑞德·门肯 拿下密歇根州
has won the state of Michigan over Jeryd Mencken.
那是15张选举人票
That's 15 electoral votes.
现在 总数是
Our tally now i goes.
各位 准备好了吗  -好吧
Are you ready for this?   -All right
门肯拿到262张选举人票
262 for Mencken
希门尼斯也是262张  -双方形成拉锯战
-and 262 for Daniel Jimenez.   -A dead heat.
阿拉斯加 即将截止投票
Polls will be closing soon in Alaska
另一个 结果还没出炉的州
the only state yet to be called other than Arizona
是 有11张选举人票的 亚利桑那
and its 11 electoral votes.
我们来问问选情专家...
Let's may be go harass the decision desk.
各位 我先来跟你们说一声
Guys just a heads-up.
选战阵营说
We hear, we are getting it from the campaign
数据人员表示 他们听说…
said the data nerds are hearing that..
阿达 你说吧
Well, Dar, you say it
亚利桑那 会被共和党拿下
So, Arizona is gonna go red.
好 那就分出胜负了吧
All right, well, then that's... that would be it, right?
威斯康辛让我们处境很为难
I mean, we're... we're kinda boxed in because of Wisconsin.
我不觉得我可以宣布结果
I mean, I... I don't feel comfortable calling it.
PGN会宣布结果 对吧 汤姆  -这个嘛...
I mean, PGN is gonna be calling it, right, Tom?   -Yeah, I mean..
他们会宣布亚利桑那的结果
I mean, they're gonna call Arizona.
如果我们宣布
Because if we call it because of Wisconsin.
而我们又说了威斯康辛悬而未决
We... We called Wisconsin pending, so..
对 我们已经宣布威斯康辛的结果了
Yeah, we already called Wisconsin.
是吧 不能反悔吧
Okay? We can't uncall Wisconsin, can we?
不然 显得很不专业
That would make us all look pretty unprofessional?
所以 亚利桑那 我们要宣布结果了
So, Arizona, we're calling the election?
对  -不行 不行
-Yeah.   -No, no.
不行吗 算一下就知道了  -不行
-No? It's math, dude.   -No.
汤姆 麻烦回避一下
Tom, will you guys give us a minute, please?
可恶  -没问题
-Fuck.   -Sure. Okay.
麻烦你们 一分钟以后回来
One minute. Be back in one minute, please.
怎样
What?
结束了啊 结束了啊  -罗曼 我不确定
-That's it, that's it.   -I don't know, Rome
也许我们该...
Like, may be... maybe we...
检讨一下威州的结果
revisit Wisconsin.
因为我们...我是说 那时有点
Because, yeah, we, I mean, we... That was kinda.
对...我懂  -对吧
Yeah... Okay, I get it.   -Right?
你现在想做大哥
No, you're gonna, like, "big brother " it right now.
你是这样打算吗
That's what you're gonna do?
不是 你在说什么
No. Like what?
就是 你想吃烤鸡
Like when, you know, if you want roast chicken
我想吃牛排 我们每次都会吃鸡肉
and I wanted steak, we always had chicken.
因为你会失控 会发飚 所以他们觉得...
Because you... you'd freak out. you had tantrums, so they thought..
我发飙 是因为永远吃不到牛排
I would fucking tantrum because I never had fucking steak
我想 他们怕的是
Well, I think they got scared if
如果你发飚就得逞 会觉得自己赢了
It's... You know, if you tantrum, then you'd think you'd won
所以 不能让你吃牛排
so they couldn't let you have the steak.
我从没赢过 每次都是吃烤鸡
I never won. It was always fucking chicken.
就因为我们小时候吃了太多鸡
So, because we had so much chicken when we were kids
我就得喜欢那个法西斯主义者吗  -对
-I have to like the fascist?   -Yeah.
如果我们 不提早宣布 而他还是赢了 这是很有可能的
If we don't call it early and he wins anyway, which is perfectly possible,
我们没有帮他 他照样胜选
which is perfectly possible, but without us tonight?
你想想会有什么后果
Think about that.
FVA和瓦利新闻支持他
With FVA and Vera News backing him
我们会成为老二 城中最没种的太监
we're left the most dickless eunuchs in cuck town
如果我们宣布了 如果我们宣布了
We call it? We call this?
如果我们推这个消息  -怎样
-We push it.   -Yeah?
也许可以成真  -对
-Maybe it happens.   -Yeah
我们说门肯胜选 门肯会阻止交易
We give it to Mencken, Mencken blocks the deal.
他不是那种优柔寡断的人 而是个汉子
He's not fuckin' wishy-washy. He's a guy.
我没什么把握 老弟 我是说
I don't know, dude. I mean...
我的孩子 这整件事…
My kids, the whole thing...
"美国”
" America."
不同的人 携手同心
Well, I mean, it is kind of a nice idea, you know?
这样的想法 蛮好的
All the different people together?
什么
What?
好 咱爸会怎么做
All right, what... what would Dad do?
你说  -我不知道
Oh, come on.   -I don't know.
我真不知道  -不知道才怪
-I don't actually know.   -Yes, you fucking do, man.
我们口袋里的人?
The guy in the pocket?
会接我们电话
The guy that's gonna answer our calls?
还会印美钞
The fucking guy printing US dollars.
这些都是好事
This is all upside
但他会让国家分裂
Apart from the matter of him smashing the country to pieces.
天啊 别这么没用
Oh, God. Don't be such a fuckin'prissy.
也许我们需要这样一个人
Okay, may be... maybe we could deal with a dose of that, right?
一个能吓吓大家的人
Like, a nice little dose of the frighteners?
让时光倒转个20年
Wind shit back 20?
你知道吗 其中一个混账 推了我女儿
You know, one of those fucking guys pushed my daughter.
她没事吧  -如果我们这么做
-She's okay?   -If we do this...
别人会说三道四的
people... people are gonna say shit
对 但我们可以进入白宫西厢
Yeah. We'll be in the West Wing
肯 这一切都不重要 完全不重要
Nothing matters, Ken. Nothing fucking matters.
爸走了 美国正等着被我们操翻
Dad's dead and the country's just a big pussy waitin' to get fucked.
他妈的行动起来 好吗
Fuckin' action, okay?
有损失 我们照价赔偿
We can pay for any damages.
咱们就 把脸埋进历史的酥胸 然后…
Let's just jam our fuckin' heads in the bosom of history and just.
对不对
Right? I mean...
或者 像落难美女一样 枯坐在一旁
Or we sit on our hands like a couple of damsels in distress
眼睁睁的 错失良机
and, you know, watch our chance slip away
PGN要宣布重大预测
PGN has a major projection to announce
那就是 杰瑞德·门肯 将会拿下亚利桑那
and that is that Jeryd Mencken will win Arizona.
他囊括了亚利桑那的11张选举人票
So, he is the winner of 11 electoral votes in Arizona.
可以谈一下吗
Can we talk for a minute?
可以 我们完蛋了 肯 我们完蛋了
Yeah, We're fucked, Ken. We're fucked
因为我们宣布了 所以完蛋了
Because we called, it's fucked
我不知道 怎么办
I don't know what we should do.
我觉得 我的头好像... 我没办法
I feel like my head is... Just, like, I can't... I can't..
我没有办法理清 眼下的状况
get the scale of it, what this is.
我们可以收回之前的预测 对吧
I mean, we can recant. Yeah?
他的团队把话说得很清楚
His team is being very direct
他们会阻止跟马特森的交易
They will block Matsson's deal
那是他说的
Well, he says he will
如果我们宣布他胜选 给他公布自己赢得大选的合法性
We call it for him, that gives him legitimacy to declare
那我们就是他的同路人了 对吧
I mean, we're in bed with him, I think, yeah?
对 我…
Yeah I.
我们说的话 上了法庭 都会是呈堂证供
I mean, it'll get ground out in the courts, whatever we say
当然 没错 但是
Sure, right, but..
听着 我们就打开天窗说亮话吧
Yeah, look, shall we be... totally honest in here?
有时候 我觉得自己做得到
I have sometimes felt like I could do it
我该这么做
You know, like I should do it. Me.
就只有我
Just me.
但是 我不希望这终结我们的家人感情
But I don't want that to be an end to the family thing, right?
我希望能 开诚布公地
I would just, I would like to be able to talk openly
讨论这种感觉
about that feeling, may be
当然 谢谢你这么说
Sure. Yeah, no, I appreciate... I appreciate that.
门肯算是罗曼的人 关系很复杂
Mencken is kinda Roman's guy, so that's complicated
没错
Yeah. Right.
老实说 他们的关系 让我倍受威胁
And, honestly, I feel... threatened, maybe, by their relationship and.
所以 我多少有点不想支持他们
So, I want... a piece of me wants to not support that.
也许是因为这样 我才不想太亲近门肯
And that's may be in there, pulling away from Mencken.
但 也因为 你是个好人
But also, you're a good guy
这我就不知道了
Well... I don't know.
你真的是  -谢谢
Sure. You are.   -Thank you.
你基本上是个好人
No, essentially, you're... you're a good guy
但 我们都想阻止马特森 对吧
But we... we all wanna stop Matsson, right?
是这样 没错吧
That's the thing?
对
Yeah.
很好 继续说
Good. Go on
我觉得...
Well, I think whatever..
作为企业的一份子
Whatever advantage to us
我们短期的优势
as... as corporate players in the short term.
你知道吗
you know...
他… 门肯是个疆梦
He's... Mencken's the nightmare
对吧
Yeah?
在这个颓丧的时代 言之成理
Plausible in a decadent era.
他的言论很邪恶 他真心相信这些邪恶的言论
He says the bad shit, he believes the bad shit
让他坐上总统位置的 不是我们
We wouldn't actually be making him president
当然 我们也许不能为他加冕
Oh, sure, we might not be able to crown him
但是 我们可以阻止他
but we can... we can stop him.
如果他今晚有了足够的声势 总统大梦就可能成真
He gets momentum tonight, it makes it possible
他需要我们宣布 他胜选的结果
He needs our call.
我觉得 自己不是个好父亲
I don't think I'm a very good father
你是 你…
You are. You're
你还可以 你尽力了
You're okay. You've tried.
我们都 只能 尽力而已
That's all we can do.
也许 我把毒害 传给下一代了  -不可能
-May be the poison drips through.   -No
不可能 你知道吗
No. And you know what?
我想 今晚连爸都不会支持他
I don't think even Dad would back him tonight
他基本上是爸钦点的
He basically picked him.
没错 但如果我们今晚全力支持他
Sure, but we throw the papers and the whole thing in for him
而一个月 或一周后
and the n in a...in a month, a week from now
法院有不同的判决
the courts go the other way?
我们这个新闻频道 就做不下去了
It's... We're essentially done as a news organization
想到 要拱手全部让给马特森 我心里就很难过
It's just hard to think we'd give it all away to Matsson
我们能不能试试 你能不能试一下
Could we try, could you try, once
直接问纳特 要他们答应 会阻止这桩交易
direct to Nate to get something from them to block the deal?
好
Yeah
好  -没问题
Yeah.   -Sure.
来 抱一下  -好
One of these?   -Yeah.
你是个好人
You're a good guy
好
Okay, yeah.
是的 我只是想问一下.
Yeah. I'm just calling with a quick... check-in inquiry
对 抱歉
-Yeah.   -We're sorry
您拨打的号码…  -老实说 我们想确认...
-The number you have reached -To be honest, I'm just wondering
希门尼斯能不能 就是...  -已经停用
-if Jimenez, I don't know..   -is not in service.
请查明后再拨
Please check the number or try your call again
现在...
So.
小西在打听 民主党能为我们做什么
Yeah, Shiv's seeing what we can get from the Dems
少来这套 为什么
Oh, get the fuck outta here. Why?
我们已经高枕无忧了  -我真的必须了解 我们在做什么
-We've got it.   -I really need to know what we're doing, guys
要不要坚持威斯康辛的开票结果.
If we wanna stick with Wisconsin and call it for...
嘿 等一下 等一下 汤姆 等一下
Hey, one moment. One moment, Tom. One moment
怎么样
So?
跟他谈过了吗
Did you talk to him?
有 我觉得有搞头
Yeah, I think there is... There's something there.
才怪
No, there's not.
什么样的搞头
Like? Like...
他们可能...他们愿意考虑一下
Like, they might be... I mean, they are willing to think.
他们可能 或是说不定 愿意考虑
Oh, they might be or maybe they are willing to think maybe
听起来狗屁不通  -不是 罗曼
-That sounds like horseshit.   -No, Rome.
他们没那么直接
They're just not so direct.
好吗 我想我们也许能让他们阻止交易
Yeah? I... I think we can probably get them to stop it
也许可能...对不起 不
Oh, they probably... Yeah, go. Sorry, no
游戏结束 放屁
Game over. Bullshit
不行 我们必须宣布 门肯很靠得住
No. We have to call it. Mencken is rock solid
罗曼 就连爸碰到这个情况
Roman, even Dad, even... even Dad in this situation
也会尊重过程
would respect the process
才不会 爸向来是为所欲为
No, Dad did whatever the fuck he wanted
他用一封传真 推翻了一个政府
He... One fax, he took out a government.
真的 他只传了“搞死莱尔”
He did, the " Fuck Lyle." Send
就完事了
And that was it. That's all it took
不管是加拿大 还是这里 他什么都不在乎
Fucking Canada, here, he didn't give a shit.
罗曼 他喜欢稳定
He liked stability, Rome.
他会步步进逼 但不会瓦解对方
He pushed, but he didn't want shit to unravel.
他协助终结...他终结了战争
He... He helped end.... I mean, he ended wars.
他终结了自己掀起的战争 他就是为所欲为
He ended wars that he started. He did whatever the fuck he wanted.
他们是怎么说的 小西 他们究竟是怎么说的
What did they say, Shiv? Like, what did Nate actually say?
他说 他会讨论一下 说 他明白我们的论点
He said they would talk and that they could see the arguments
我觉得 还蛮有希望的
and I... I think it's encouraging.
你觉得蛮有希望  -是 很有希望啊
You felt like it was encouraging? ?   -It was. It was encouraging
原来是你的感觉 我有比较具体的东西
It was a feeling. I got something real.
这完全没有意义 真是浪费时间
This is fucking pointless. What a waste of time.
你在干吗  -我要打电话
What are you doing?   -I'm gonna call
我要挑明了说...
I... I'm just gonna... I'm gonna be very direct.
我们只要多一点...
We just... We just need a little bit more.
别打给他  -为什么
Don't call him.   -Why?
他们很忙啊
They're... They're busy.
绝对不能有任何不确定性 想想该死的市场
Can't have uncertainty. Can't. Fucking market.
重新投票造成的混乱
The chaos of trying to rerun an entire election
可能会让国家崩溃
could just send the country into meltdown, you know?
你提出的是恶意论点  -我跟你说
Okay, bad faith argument.   -I'm telling you.
我只是在跟你说 不能有任何不确定性
I'm just telling you, you can not have uncertainty.
中国就要来了  -中国就要来了?
-China is coming.   -China is coming?
中国要来了  -中国已经来了 下一个
China's coming.   --China's already been. Next.
这又不是最终结果
It's not like the fucking final, final, anyway
还有法院判决 和其他杂事
Okay, there's the court shit and it all kinda just fuzz es along, you know?
根本是浪费时间
It's just waste of fucking time.
且 我们已经没有时间了
That we don't have, by the way
嘿 格雷格 我可以问你一个问题吗
Hey, Greg, can I ask you a question?
什么事
What's up?
你是不是知道什么内情...
Do you know if there's something going on..
纳特 吉尔 和该死的希门尼斯 还说要给你什么
What else Nate and Gil and fucking Jimenez offer you?
让你用一招半式 就取得 用不完的社会福利开支?
Unlimited social security spending with this one weird trick?
那通电话聊得如何
How was that call?
有什么收获? 两手空空?
What'd you get? Whole bunch of not much?
真的吗
Really?
什么事
What?
我觉得你是个好人?
" I think you're a good guy?'
我联络不上纳特 所以 归纳了一些印象
Well, I found it hard to get Nate so I summarized some impressions.
是啦...很聪明 真有你的 小西
Oh, right... Smart. Really good, Shiv
但你说谎了 对不对
But you lied. Right?
纳特没给她任何保证  -真的吗
She didn't get anything from Nate.   -Really?
她没跟纳特联络上 她跟马特森是一伙的
She didn't speak to Nate. And she's in with Matsson
对不起 你说什么  -不是 我...不
Sorry, what?   -No. I.. No.
不是...我...我做了我们一致同意的事
No, I... I did what we all agreed to.
去接近他 这样才能帮你们
that I got close to him so that I could help for the
她在搞我们 对吧
Shiv's fucking us, right?
对吧 小西
Right, Shivy?
没有...
No.
我...  -我...
I...was...
我刚问了你一些很认真的问题 小西
I fucking asked you some real questions, Shiv
还纳闷 你为什么坐立不安
I wondered why you looked like a goose
你这个小人
trying to shit a house brick, you piece of dirt
所以 你私下跟敌人交易?
Okay, what, you got yourself a little fuck in'side deal here?
不是 不是 我有几个选择
No, no. I have some options.
我...我照我们的计划行事
I... I was... I was going through with the plan
但你们两个...  -所以 是门肯 门肯对吧?
-and then you two...   -Well, Mencken. Mencken, right?
门肯  -不 什么
-Mencken.   -No. What?
汤姆
Tom!
不行 你连我们都想一脚踢开
No, you even wanted to push us, us out of the fucking nest.
是啦 妹妹 是啦...  -拜托
Sure, sis. Sure...   -Please.
肯 撇开这些先不说 你这样做不对
Ken, aside from all this, this is not the right thing.
你是 除了你骗我们
Aside from the fact that you lied to us
为自己的私利着想吗
and that doing what you want precisely plays into your own interests, yeah?
而这就不是吗 是吗
Oh, and this doesn't? Yeah?
肯 拜托 拜托 我们是什么人
Ken, please, come on. Come on, who are we?
怎么都没有为孩子们着想
Oh, well, " Will no one think of the children?'
告诉你 我会阻止这件事的
You know what? No, I'm not gonna let this happen.
总有一天 你必须挺身而出...
There comes a time when you have to stand
总有一天.
" There comes a time.
我是认真的 好吗
Seriously. This is real. Okay?
我很担心共和国
I have a concern for the state of the republic
和 多元化的状况
and... and pluralism and..
还有 这个国家的未来  -好无聊
and the future of this country.   -So boring
这些都是真的  -听你在这放屁 天啊
And it... And it is real.   -You're such a bore, Shiv. Jesus.
你去死 肯
Fuck you. Ken?
他说得对
He's right.
对 你好无聊
Yeah. You're boring
而且 你没有进来这里的通行证
And you don't have a pass for in here.
好 知道吗 也许我
Okay, well, fine. You know what? I'm... I'm... May be I'll go...
会公开这一切
I'l...'ll go public.
是吗  -我就去找报社
yeah?   -I'll go to the papers and people
告诉他们 你们干的好事
and tell 'em what you're actually fucking doing, which is..
如果你要胡闹
If you're just gonna be hysterical
我们得请你离开
we're gonna have to, you know, ask you to leave
你去死  -这里的人有正事要干
-Fuck you.   -People are trying to do some serious work in here
你去死 这 事关国家的未来
Fuck you. This is about the future of the country
不对 我想是因为 你跟男朋友分手了
No, I think it's because you broke up with your boyfriend
你真的很贱  -大家好
Jesus, you're a prick.   -Hello
宣布吧 你可以宣布了  -不行
So, call it. You can call it.   -No
我们要宣布了吗  -对 我们已宣布威州的结果
-We're calling it?   -Yeah, we called Wisconsin
现在宣布亚利桑那 就决定大选结果
now we're gonna call Arizona, so we call the election.
要宣布了吗  -宣布吧
We call the election?   -Call it.
宣布吧  -不行 不行 汤姆
-Call it.   -No. No, Tom.
不行 这是大错特错 拜托你 不要
No. You're making a terrible mistake. Please don't
嘿 各位 这轮不到我决定
Hey, guys, it's not my call.
这 轮不到我决定
It's not my call.
好 由我们决定  -要由你们决定
Okay. It's our call.   -It's your call. It's up to you.
你们若决定好了...  -我决定了
If you say so.   -I say so.
你们就是他妈的 本丢·彼拉多
Fucking Pontius Pilate.
没人在乎 没人在乎
No one cares. No one... no one cares.
嘿  -嘿 跟他们说 我要下来了
Hey, yeah.   -Hey. Tell'em I'm coming down.
对 我们要宣布了
Yes. We're gonna call it.
我们要宣布门肯胜选  -好的
-Yeah, we're calling for Mencken.   -All right.
跟他们说 我要来了 好
Okay, tell'em I'm coming. All right
好了 做得好 汤姆
-Okay.   -Great work, Tom.
谢谢
Thank you.
干得好 好精彩的一夜
Good stuff. Great night.
该死的
Fuck.
你还好吗
You okay?
还好 我…
Yeah. I.
我得去告诉他们
I have to go... tell them.
我们好像要宣布门肯胜选
I think, we're callin'it. For Mencken.
对啊
Yeah.
我得走了  -对
-So, I should... I should go.   -Right. Yeah.
再不走 会有麻烦的
I'll get in trouble if I don't go.
好 老兄 我是说
Okay, dude. I mean..
对 这反正不是我的选择 对吧
Yeah, I mean, it's not really my choice, right?
当然 你说得对 对
Sure. I mean, right. Yeah
我只是负责按钮
Yeah, I'm just... I'm pressing the button.
甚至不是按钮
Or I'm not even pressing the button, I'm...
而是叫他们准备按钮
I'm asking them to prepare to press the button.
对 就像发动核武攻击一样
Right, and all that does is just, like, launch a nuclear attack.
那
So...
反正 我不去 也不会改变什么 所以...
It's not gonna change anything if I don't go, so..
就两分钟而已
Couple minutes. So, I mean..
对啊 对啊
Right, right.
实际而言.
Realistically.
好疯狂  -是啊
-Crazy.   -Yeah.
疯狂
Crazy
今晚真的好疯狂
Crazy one.
汤姆刚刚跟我说了
So, Tom just told me.
各位 宣布门肯胜选
Everybody, calling it for Mencken
他要宣布门肯胜选
He's calling it for Mencken.
听到了吗  -他说了
-Everybody.   -What he said, yeah?
我刚说了  -我要宣布门肯胜选
I just said.   -I'm... I'm calling it for Mencken
好的
Okay.
好吗  -好 是的
Okay.   -Okay. Yeah.
好 那么戴夫
Okay. Well, then, Dave?
好 莉蒂亚 准备好"门肯胜选”
Okay. Lydia, get me " Mencken Wins."
开始倒数计时 泛美网科的各位
Get the ticker going on ATN Citizens.
把消息传出去 说 泛美网科两分钟后 宣布大选结果
Let the people know two mins and ATN is gonna call it.
我们现在要宣布了
We are gonna make this call now.
泛美网科选情专家看了数据...
The ATN Decision Desk has looked at the numbers..
准备宣布 杰瑞德·门肯 拿下亚利桑那
and is ready to declare Arizona for Jeryd Mencken
这表示 门肯将是下一届美国总统
This means that Mencken will be the next president of the United States
他赢得了美国史上
winning the most unreal, surreal election
最不真实的总统大选
we have ever seen in this country
他六个月前 才在维吉尼亚宣布出马 角逐总统大位
his candidacy starting in Virginia only six months ago
在总统表示不寻求连任之后
against a dozen other Republican candidates
与共和党十几名其他候选人激战
in the wake of the President saying he wasn't going to run for re-election
原本不可能实现的目标
What started off as an unlikely impossibility
如今成了现实 门肯胜选了
now a reality, it is Mencken
好吧
Well...
看来已经确定了 我拿到足够的候选人票
It's now clear I have won sufficient electoral votes..
成为美国的下一任总统
to be declared the next president of the United States
我觉得 这是很棒的重责大任
and I find the responsibility awesome.
我知道 还有人觉得有争议
Now, I know there are some who feel there is something left to contest
但是 人民投了票 票数也统计完毕
But votes have been cast, votes have been tallied
也许 在别的日子 别的时刻
On another day, in another time
会有不同的结果
they might have fallen in another fashion
但 向来以正直著称的组织 宣布我胜选了
The election has been called for me by an authority of known integrity
要不要找个历史学家来
Maybe we should get, like, a history guy?
一个真正的书虫
You know, like a brain, like a real brainiac
解释 为什么过去发生过这种事
to say why this sort of thing has happened in the past
说 一切都会没事的
and that it'll all be fine?
我要对批评我的人说
To my critics
我不是个焗动民心的政客
I am not a demagogue
我是民主的捍卫者
I am a defender of democracy.
但是 民主有一个我们必须提防的倾向
But democracy, it has this tendency that we have to beware
那就是 成为纯粹的交易
to become mere transaction.
一物换一物
I give you this. You give me that
我求你投票给我
I come begging for your vote.
拿出社会福利支票
Welfare checkbook out.
为社会福利国王和王后加冕
Crowning the welfare kings and queens
直到所有人 都成为小小的独裁者
until everyone has become a little tyrant
由国家加冕
crowned by the state
我遵循的模式 不是来自被烧成焦土的市场
The model that I follow isn't from the scorched marketplace
狡猾的商人在市场上讨价还价
where cunning men haggle for the best price
那不是我的作风
That's not me.
我信仰的民主制度
The democracy I believe in
领导人来自群众
is where a leader emerged from the people
几乎是凭借着意志力而出线
willed, almost, into being
因这个共和国的人民
brought forth by the great sweetness of the virtue
集体的智慧 和善良而显现
of the combined wisdom of the good people of this republic
在这片污染的大地
Don't we long, sometimes
我们偶尔
for something clean
都会渴望拥有干净的事物
once in this polluted land?
我要给各位的 就是这样的东西
That's what I hope to bring.
不是经过妥协后的秽物
Not something grubby with compromise
而是干净 真实 而清新的事物
Something clean and true and refreshing
他是个可以跟我们做生意的人
He's a guy we can do business with.
对  -骄傲 而纯粹的事物
-Yeah.   -Something proud and pure
他会合作的  -谢谢大家
-He'll play ball.   -Thank you very much
你该听听 他是怎么谈半导体的
You should hear him talk semiconductors.
天佑美国  -掌握大权的是市场
-And God bless the United States of America.   -The market's holding the leash
我们只是做了一晚精彩的电视节目
We just made a night of good TV.
如此而已 什么都不会发生
That's what we've done. Nothing happens
会发生的 罗曼
Things do happen, Rome
总统来电
President calling.
坐上大位的总统大人 有何贵千
Hocus-POTUS. Sitting in the POTUS position. What's up?
嘿 我现在没时间 但是谢谢你
Hey, man. I... Look, no time, but just, just thanks, yeah?
你我联手 会走得长远
You and me, man. We'll go far.
走到对街的酒吧喝酒
Over the road and into the bar.
一场前所未见的总统大选
an election unlike anything we've ever seen
紧接着 是一段永垂不朽的演讲
followed by a speech for the ages.
法律程序会很冗长
The legal process is gonna be lengthy.
你觉得什么时候会结束
When do you think it'll all be over?
可能会持续三个月
This... this could be going on for the next three months.
嘿 汤姆 你的电话
Hey, Tom? Your phone.
响个不停 汤姆
It's... It's red hot, Tom. It..
很多重要的大人物想骂你
A lot of very important people wanna scream at you.
这有点太刻薄了
This is a little pointed
泛美网科的老板 汤姆·威姆士丹
..by ATN boss Tom Wambsgans
达温想知道 何时要让他受访
Darwin wants to know when to do his caveats
有时间采访他吗
Is there time for him to do it?
没有
No.
不确定威姆士丹的行为
So, it's unclear whether Wa mbs gans'alleged action
是否为误判  -喂
-was an error of judgment -Hello?
还是人为  -不
or there was a personal -No
或者政治力干预的结果
or political dimension to the decision.
大家都知道 他跟杰瑞德·门肯过从甚密
He is, of course, known to be an associate of Jeryd Mencken.
怎么回事  -那些假数据?
-What's going on?   -Those funky numbers?
我寄稿子给你
I'm sending you words, yeah?
接下来24小时内 一定要公布 反正新闻多得很
Let's get 'em out in the next 24. Lot of fuckin' news.
你们疯了
You guys are crazy.
卢卡斯 这不只是单纯的发疯而已
Yeah, it's more than just fucking crazy, Lukas
对 但这实在太疯狂了
No, but this is crazy.
对 我们会反击的
Yeah, well, we're gonna do a number on 'em.
我们会狠狠地反击 我们会搞定的 好吗
We're gonna fuck them so hard we're gonna fix this, yeah?
操
Fuck
我可以来看孩子们吗
Can I come see the kids?
他们都睡了 肯  -就...我知道
They're asleep, Ken.   -Just... I know. Yeah
我可以等他们醒来
Well, I can... I can wait up for them
我也早该睡了 但是我睡不着
I should be asleep, but I... I can't
好 明天见
Okay, I'll... I'll see you tomorrow.
明天葬礼时见 好吗
I'll see you at the funeral. Okay?
费克雷 有些人就是谈不成交易
Some people just can't cut a deal, Fikret